[ Music ]
[音乐]
[ Applause ]
[掌声]
&gt;&gt; Hello and welcome.
&gt;&gt;  欢迎大家
I'm Lindsay Verity from
我是来自广告平台的
Advertising Platforms and I'll
Lindsay Verity
be joined by my colleague, Carol
今天 我将和同事
Hsu, and we're here today to
Carol Hsu 一起
tell you what's new in Search
和你们讨论搜索广告的
Ads.
新功能
Search Ads was first introduced
搜索广告于 2016 年 10 月
to the App Store in the U.S. in
首次在美国的 App Store
October 2016 as an efficient and
推出 作为一种高效便捷的方式
easy way for you to promote your
你可以
apps directly in App Store
直接在 App Store 的
search results so customers
搜索结果中推广你的 App
could discover your apps while
客户可以在保护他们隐私的同时
protecting their privacy.
发现你的 App
Search Ads Advanced has since
高级搜索广告
expanded to the App Stores in
已经扩展到
the U.K., Australia, New
英国 澳大利亚 新西兰
Zealand, Canada, Switzerland,
加拿大、瑞士和墨西哥
and Mexico.
的 App Store
In December 2017, we introduced
2017 年 12 月 我们将
Search Ads Basic to the App
基础版搜索广告引进了
Store in the U.S., a minimal
美国的 App Store
effort cost-per-install offering
并且它的安装成本极少
that's fast become a favorite of
这使其快速成为
developers worldwide to promote
全球开发者用来
their apps on the U.S. App
在美国 App Store 上
Store.
推广其 App 的最爱
And the response to Search Ads
所有类型的开发者
from developers of all types has
对搜索广告的反应都是
been incredible.
认为这是难以置信的
Postsnap, a U.K.-based photocard
Postsnap 是一个总部位于英国的
app has used Search Ads to
照片卡 App 它使用搜索广告
expand their offering to new
将其产品扩展到新的市场
markets and they told us Search
它们告诉我们 搜索广告
Ads has given us a huge increase
为它们在多个地区的
in high-value users in multiple
高价值用户的数量带来了
regions.
巨大的增长
Now we're using Search Ads to
现在我们使用搜索广告
help us launch other apps too.
来帮助我们启动其他 App
And JoyTunes, creators of
仪器学习 App
instrument learning apps, are
的创造者 JoyTunes
seeing incredible results.
正在见证令人难以置信的结果
They say the quality of users is
他们表示用户的质量
so good that the numbers
非常好
upgrading from free to
从免费升级到付费订阅的数量
subscription is double that of
是其他任何
any other pay channel.
付费频道的两倍
And, for Playtika's World Series
而且 对于 Playtika 的
of Poker, it's the quality and
世界扑克系列来说
engagement of users that matters
重要的是用户的质量和参与度
and they said Search Ads is an
他们说搜索广告是一个
extremely powerful product that
非常强大的产品
has brought high-quality users
它带来了高质量的用户
and engagement rates 10% higher
且参与率比平均值
than the average.
高出 10%
It's been really great and
听到这些故事
wonderful hearing these stories
真的是太棒了
and so many more like them.
还有更多这类的故事
And so, today, I'm excited to
今天 我很高兴地
announce that this summer,
宣布 今年夏天
Search Ads Advanced is coming to
Search Ads Advanced （高级搜索广告）
six more app stores.
即将推出六个 App Store
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
Thank you.
谢谢
Japan, South Korea, Germany,
日本 韩国 德国
France, Italy, and Spain, giving
法国 意大利和西班牙
you even more opportunities to
给你更多的机会来
reach high-intent, high-quality
使你在更多你曾说过的
users in more of the markets
你认为的最重要的市场中
you've told us are most
接触高意向
important to you.
高质量的用户
And, what's more, we'll be
此外 我们还将
introducing Search Ads Basic to
向所有 13 家可以使用搜索广告的
all 13 App Stores where Search
App Store 推出
Ads will be available.
Search Ads Basic （基础版搜索广告）
And we've worked hard to make
我们一直在努力确保
sure that Search Ads Basic
Search Ads Basic
remains a simple, easy,
仍然是一个简单 容易
effortless way for you to
毫不费力的方式
promote your apps across
来在多个 App Store
multiple app stores.
推广你的 App
Let me show you how easy it's
让我告诉你这将会是
going to be.
多么容易
Imagine I'm a developer and I
要知道我是一名开发人员
want to start to promote my new
我想开始推广我的新 App
app, NoMoss.
NoMoss
I simply select the app from the
我只需从下拉列表中
drop-down list and note that I
选择 App
know see an ad example on the
看到我右边有一个广告例子
right and I'm also presented
我还会看到搜索广告
with a list of the app stores
可用的 App Store 列表
where Search Ads is available
以及我的 NoMoss App
and also where my NoMoss app is
可用的
available too.
位置
I want to permit my app in as
我想让我的 App
many app stores as I can and so
在尽可能多的 App Store 里
I'm going to leave all of those
因此我将保留所有
selected.
选定的 App Store
Next, I enter my monthly budget,
接下来 进入我的每月预算
which is a single budget across
这是一个单一的预算
all of the app stores where my
包括所有的 App Store
app promotion will run.
我的 App 将在这里推广运行
My monthly budget for NoMoss is
我每月的 NoMoss 预算
$5000.
是 5000 美元
the maximum amount I'm willing
我愿意为安装
to pay for an install.
支付的最大金额
Now, note Search Ads is
现在 请注意 搜索广告
recommending a maximum
建议的最高安装费用
cost-per-install of $1.50, which
为 1.50 美元
is based on what it knows about
这是基于它对我的 App 的了解
my app and also what similar
以及类似的 App
apps are willing to pay for an
愿意为安装付费
install, so I'm going to take
的情况 所以我将
that recommendation.
采用这个建议
I then save and I'm taken to my
然后我保存这个建议并将其
dashboard where I'll check back
带入仪表板 稍后我会再检查一次
later to see the results.
以查看结果
I can now see confirmation that
现在 我可以看到并确认
my new app promotion has been
我的新 App 升级
saved and it should start
已经被保存 并且它应该
running soon.
很快可以开始运行
From my dashboard, I can also
在我的仪表板中
add another app that I want to
我还可以添加其他我想
promote and I can also make
推广的 App
changes to any of my existing
还可以对我现有的提升程序
app promotions.
进行更改
So, I am currently running
因此我目前正在
promotions in the U.S. App Store
在美国的 App Store 中
for my LightRight app and I'd
为我的 LightRight App 升级运行
like to expand that to more app
并且希望将其扩展到
stores.
更多 App Store
To do that, I simply click on
要做到这一点 我只需点击
the edit button at the top of
App 卡顶部的
the apps card and my LightRight
编辑按钮
app is only available in 10 of
LightRight App 只能在 10 个
the app stores where Search Ads
App Store 提供搜索广告
is offered, so I'm only
所以我只
presented with those 10 options.
介绍这 10 个选项
Now, I can pick markets
现在 我可以单独挑选市场
individually, Canada and France,
例如加拿大和法国
for example, or I can select
或者我可以全部
all.
选择
I save. And I can now see that
我保存了 我现在可以看到
my app is being promoted in 10
我的 App 正在 10 个
of 10 available app stores.
可用的 App Store 中被推广
Now, because I'm promoting my
现在由于我在更多
app across more app stores, I
App Store 中宣传我的 App
also want to increase my monthly
因此我还希望增加每月预算
budget to enable me to reach
使我能够接触
more users and achieve more
更多用户并实现更多
installs, so I'm going to change
的安装 所以我将
my monthly budget from $1000 to
每月预算从 1000 美元
$3500.
更改为 3500 美元
My change is saved and I'm done.
我的修改被保存了 我完成了
It's really that simple and we
这真的很简单
can't wait for more of you to
我们迫不及待想要你们
try it.
来尝试
And that was Search Ads Basic.
这就是 Search Ads Basic
So, let's talk about Advanced
那么 我们来讨论一下高级广告搜索
and, more specifically, new
更具体来说
creative options.
是新的创意选项
Developers have told us they
开发人员告诉我们
love the ease of Search Ads
他们喜欢 Search Ads Creative
Creative and how we
的便利性 以及我们如何
automatically create the ads
使用元数据和图像
using the metadata and imagery
来自动创建广告并
you already provide for your App
提供给你的 App Store
Store product page.
产品页面
And App Store customers respond
App Store 的用户
really well to those ads because
对这些广告做出了非常好的反应
of their noninvasive appearance
不仅因为它们非侵入式的外观
and because they're an accurate
还因为它们准确地
representation of what they can
表达了
expect from the app's
对 App 体验的
experience.
期望
Since February, you've had the
自 2 月份以来
option to add up to 10 app
你可以选择在 App Store
screenshots and 3 videos on your
产品页面上 添加 10 个 App 截图
App Store product page.
和 3 个视频
And just last week, we were
就在上周 我们
excited to introduce our newest
介绍了我们最新的
Search Ads Advanced feature,
Search Ads Advanced
Creative Sets, giving you the
创意集 让你
ability to leverage these
有能力利用这些
additional App Store assets to
额外的 App Store 资产
create more ad variations to
创建更多广告变体
help you better align your ad
以帮助您更好地
group keyword themes with
将广告组关键字主题
specific audiences.
与特定受众群体进行匹配
Now, let me turn it over to
现在 接下来的内容将交给
Carol, who's going to tell you
Carol 他会告诉你
more about how Creative Sets
更多关于创意集
work and give you a demo.
的工作方式并给你做演示
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
&gt;&gt; Thanks, Lindsay.
&gt;&gt; 感谢 Lindsay
As Lindsay just showed, you can
正如 Lindsay 刚刚展示的
use Creative Sets to display
你可以使用创意集
different app previews in
在屏幕截图中
screenshots that align to
显示不同的 App 预览
keyword themes or specific
以便于使关键字主题或特定的
audiences.
受众群体保持一致
Since Creative Sets uses App
由于创意集使用了
Store approved assets, this
App Store 认可的资产
ensures the best user
这确保了最佳的
experience.
用户体验
I'm here to show you how it's
这里 我将向你展示
done.
它是如何完成的
Before we begin, imagine I'm a
在开始之前 想象一下
developer and these are all of
我是一名开发人员
the assets that I've uploaded to
我的 App 我将这些上传到
App Store Connect for my app,
App Store
TripTrek.
TripTrek
TripTrek is an app that lets
TripTrek 是一款让
users document every step of
用户记录旅行和徒步
their travels and treks.
步数的 App
The first three assets will be
前三个资产将
used in my default ad.
用于我的默认广告
The default ad matches what
默认广告匹配
shows in organic search results;
自然搜索结果中显示的内容
however, there are 2 specific
不过 有 2 个特定的
keyword themes that I want to
关键字主题
focus on with my Search Ads
我想集中在我的搜索广告当中
campaigns, fitness and mapping.
健身和映射
I can use Creative Sets to
我可以使用创意集
choose the assets that best
来选择最适合
align to those themes.
这些主题的资产
Let's go through the steps of
让我们来看看
how I do that by adding Creative
通过将创意集添加到我的
Sets to my Search Ads campaigns
搜索广告系列和广告组来了解
and ad groups now.
我是如何实现这一点
Here I am, already logged into
在这里 我已登录到
my Search Ads account.
我的搜索广告帐户
And I'm on the campaigns view.
我正在参与广告系列视图
Let's go ahead and create a new
让我们继续并共同创建
campaign together.
一个新的活动
I'll start by clicking Create
我将首先点击创建
Campaign, choosing my app,
广告系列选择我的 App
TripTrek, the storefront that I
TripTrek 我想将其
want to promote it in, and I'll
推广到的店面
give it a campaign name.
然后给它一个广告系列名称
Let's call this one Active
我们称之为
Travel.
主动旅行
I'll assign a budget and for now
我会分配一个预算
I'll skip over the daily cap and
现在我将跳过每日上限和
the campaign negative keywords.
广告系列否定关键字
We'll go ahead and create the
我们将继续创建
first ad group in this campaign.
此广告系列中的第一个广告组
I'm going to call it fitness to
我将它称之为健身
match the keywords that I plan
以匹配我计划投标的
to bid on.
关键词
I want this to run on both iPad
我想让它在 iPad
and iPhone, so I'll leave that
和 iPhone 上运行 所以我会
setting as is.
保持原样
And since, of course, I want
当然 因为 我希望
this to run all day every day,
每天都这样运行
I'll leave the ad scheduling
所以我现在只剩下
alone for now.
广告日程安排了
And I'll enter a default max CPT
我将输入默认的最高
bid.
CPT 出价
I'm going to leave Search Match
现在搜索匹配
on so that Search Ads
以便搜索广告
automatically matches my ads to
自动将我的广告
relevant searches.
与相关搜索进行匹配
And I'm going to choose from
我将从
some of the recommended keywords
一些推荐的关键字中
some of the keywords that match
选择一些与我的健身主题
my fitness theme.
相匹配的关键字
Maybe we'll go with hiking
也许我们会带着徒步旅行跟踪器
tracker, hiking trails, activity
登山步道 活动跟踪器
tracker, and step counter.
和步计数器
And then I'll add a few more of
然后我会再添加一些
my own.
我自己的设备
How about fitness tracker and
那么健身追踪器
fitness challenge, since that's
和健身挑战怎么样呢
one of the features in my app.
这是我的 App 中的一个功能特征
Since I want my ads to show to
我想让我的广告
all users, I'll leave the
向所有的用户展示
audience settings alone for now
所以我现在也会把观众的设置
too.
单独放在一边
Here I can see a preview of the
在这里 我可以看到
default text ad and the default
默认文本广告和默认图像广告的预览
image ad, which shows alongside
它显示了在我的
the ads from my Creative Sets
创意集旁边的广告
and matches the organic search
并匹配有机
result.
搜索结果
But, since I want to use assets
但是 由于我想使用
that are more closely aligned to
更贴近我的健身主题的资产
my fitness theme, I'm going to
所以我要
create a Creative Set for that,
为它创建一个创意集
so let's go ahead and add one
所以让我们继续
now by clicking Add Creative
点击添加
Set.
创意集
I'll name this Creative Set
我将命名这个创意集
Social Hiking and choose the
为社会远足 并选择
localization language.
本地化语言
The set of languages depends on
这套语言取决于
the storefronts that I'm
我所推广的店面
promoting in and on the
以及我提交给
localized assets that I
App Store Connect 的
submitted to App Store Connect.
本地化资产
I'll leave this as English for
现在我会把它
now.
设为英文
Next, I need to choose the right
接下来 我需要选择正确的
combination of assets to create
资产组合来创建
an effective creative set.
有效的创意集
Here I can see all of the
在这里 我可以看到
screenshots and app previews
我的 App 产品页面上的
from the available set of assets
可用资产集合中的
on my app product page organized
所有屏幕截图和 App 预览
by display size and in the order
并按照我提交给
that I submitted to App Store
App Store Connect 的顺序进行
Connect.
组织
I'll only see the display sizes
我只看到有足够的
that have enough localized
本地化资产
assets to satisfy a Creative
以满足创意集的
Set.
显示尺寸
In App Store Connect, I had
在 App Store Connect 中
elected to use the 5.5-inch
我选择使用 5.5 英寸的显示器
display, which is why I don't
这就是为什么
see any other iPhone display
我在这里看不到其他 iPhone
size assets here.
显示屏尺寸的原因
If I'm having trouble
如果我无法
remembering which devices are
记住哪些设备
which display size, I can go to
的显示尺寸 我可以
the upper right-hand corner and
转到右上角
click on View Device Display
点击查看设备显示尺寸
Sizes to see that information.
以查看该信息
I'll go ahead and close this
我现在就继续
now.
并关闭它
If I hover over an asset, an
如果我将鼠标悬停在资产上
icon appears in the lower
左下角会出现一个图标，
left-hand corner and I can click
我可以点击该图标
on that to get a closer look.
进行仔细查看
I can also easily click through
我也可以轻松点击
to see the other assets as well.
查看其他资产
Let me close this now and choose
现在我们关闭它
the assets for my Creative Set.
为我的创意集选择资产
For the iPhone 5.5-inch display,
对于 iPhone 5.5 英寸显示器来说
I have all portrait assets, so I
我拥有所有肖像资产
need to select at least 3 in
因此我需要选择至少 3 个
order to complete my Creative
才能完成
Set.
我的创意集
I can see which of my assets are
我可以通过此标签
already being used in the
查看默认广告中
default ads by this label here
哪些资产已被默认广告使用
that says default on the first
并在前几个资产上显示
few assets.
默认广告
I'm going to choose assets that
我将选择
are different from the default
与默认主题不同的资产
ones and that are aligned with
并与我的健身主题
my fitness theme.
保持一致
Here we go.
我们开始
These look good.
这些看起来不错
And then for the iPad 12.9-inch
然后 对于 iPad 12.9 英寸的
display size, I have all
显示尺寸
landscape assets, so I need to
我有所有的景观资产 所以我需要
select at least one of these in
至少选择其中之一
order for my ads to show on
以便我的广告显示在
iPad.
iPad 上
I'll go ahead and pick this one
我现在就继续
for now.
选择这个
Once I've chosen assets for each
为每一个尺寸选择资产
display size, I click save and
我点击保存
see that my creative set has
并看到我的创意集
been added to my ad group and
已经添加到我的广告组
now I'm ready to start my
现在我已准备好开始
campaign.
我的广告系列
The Active Travel campaign now
主动旅行系列现在
appears on my campaigns view and
出现在我的广告系列视图中
that's how you add a Creative
这就是您将创意集
Set to a new campaign and ad
添加到新活动和广告组
group.
的方式
Next, let me show you how to add
接下来 让我为你们展示怎样添加
a Creative Set to an existing
一个 Creative Set 到现有的
campaign and ad group.
系列和广告组
Let's go into my Navigation
让我们一起进入 我的导航
campaign.
系列
And from there, let's go into
从那里 我们会走进
the City Maps ad group and I'll
城市地图广告组 我将会
click on this new Creative Sets
点击这个新的创意集
tab.
选项卡
This is a brand-new view in
这是搜索广告中的
Search Ads where I'll be able to
全新视图 在这里我不仅可以
see not only how my Creative
看到我的创意集的效果
Sets are performing, but also
还可以看到
how the default text ad and the
默认文字广告和
default image ad are doing.
默认图片广告的效果
I currently only have the
目前我只有
default ads running and I don't
默认广告正在投放
have any Creative Sets yet for
而没有任何广告组的
this ad group.
创意集
So, I'll add one now by clicking
所以 我现在通过点击
Add Creative Set.
添加创意集来添加一个
Let's go ahead and name this
我们继续 把这个命名为
Creative Set Mapping Features to
创意集映射特征
align to my mapping theme.
与我的映射主题保持一致
And I'll leave the localization
而且我将把本地
language as English again.
语言再次改为英文
And for the iPhone 5.5-inch
对于 iPhone 5.5 英寸
display size, I have all
显示尺寸 我拥有所有
portrait assets, so again I need
肖像资产 所以我需要
to select at least 3 to populate
至少再挑选三个来填充
my ad.
我的广告
In this case, I'm going to
在这种情况下 我将
choose more than 3 assets,
选择超过三个资产
including some that are already
其中包括已经
used in the default ads, and let
在默认广告中使用的资产
Search Ads automatically create
并让搜索广告自动地为
the various combinations of ads
所有这些资产创建
from all of these assets.
各种各样的广告组合
Search Ads uses machine learning
搜索广告使用机器学习
to continuously optimize to show
来持续不断优化
the best performing ads.
以选出最好的广告
Since I'm only interested in
由于我只对
testing ad variations for iPhone
测试 iPhone 的广告变化感兴趣
at this time, I'm going to elect
所以这一次 我将选择
to use default assets for iPad,
为 iPad 使用默认的资产
which means only the default ads
这意味着只有默认的广告
will show on iPad.
才会显示在 iPad 上
I click save and now I've added
点击保存 现在我为广告组添加了
my first Creative Set to this ad
我的第一套创意广告集
group and I can create up to 10
在每一个广告组中 我可以创造
Creative Sets per ad group.
多达 10 个创意集。
I can return to this view at any
我可以随时返回这个视图
time to check how this Creative
来查看这个创意集的效果
Set is performing versus the
与默认广告
default ads.
的效果
So, that's how I added Creative
所以 这就是我如何
Sets for my two keyword themes,
为我的两个关键字主题
fitness and mapping.
健身和映射添加创意素材集
I hope you'll give this a try
我希望你可以自己
yourself.
试一试
Now, let me hand it back to
接下来的内容 让我们交给
Lindsay.
Lindsay
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
&gt;&gt; Thank you, Carol.
&gt;&gt; 谢谢 Carol
Thank you.
谢谢
So, to summarize, Creative Sets
总而言之 创意集
use App Store approved assets,
使用 App Store 通过的资产
so it continues ensuring a
所以能够继续确保
really great customer
非常出色的
experience.
客户体验
And now with more ad variations,
现在 随着更多的广告变体
you can more closely align your
你可以更加紧密的将
ad images to specific keyword
广告图像与受众群体的
themes for audiences and our
特定的关键词主题相匹配
machine learning ensures you'll
并且我们的机器学习保证你将
always achieve the best results.
始终获得最佳效果
It's been great sharing these
很高兴今天能与你们
updates with you today.
分享这些新功能
Just to recap, Search Ads
回顾一下
Advanced is coming to 6 more
今年夏天 高级搜索广告将
markets this summer and Basic
进入 6 个市场 另外基础版将
will be coming to all 13 App
推出全部 13 个
Stores where Search Ads is
可使用搜索广告
available.
的 App Store
Creative Sets are available now,
创意集现在就可使用
so if you're a Search Ads
所以如果你是一名
Advanced user, start
高级搜索广告用户
experimenting with different ad
可开始尝试使用不容的广告
variations and see how they can
变体 了解他们如何
further improve the performance
进一步提高现有广告的
of your existing campaigns.
效果
And we really love to hear from
我们非常愿意
you on your experiences with
聆听你们对于这个新功能的
this new feature.
体验感受
As always, you can learn more at
与往常一样 你可以在
our website,
我们的网站
searchads.apple.com.
searchads.apple.com 了解更多信息
Thank you so much for listening.
感谢你们的到来
It's been really great sharing
很高兴能与你们
this with you today.
一同分享
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]